Let's go! You can do it, Kuribayashi!
Come on, show him what experience made of!
Visualize it.
What I'd be doing in his place.
I'd be more grateful to be there than that guy.
The jealousy is real, my friends.
Kuribayashi, take it away!
Fast pressing by Tosu.
Watch out! He's gonna tackle you!
He passed him!
Just when you thought he was in danger, Kuribayashi pulled out.
He took advantage of the other player's momentum, and then he mowed right past him.
A blindsiding move.
You were one step behind.
Tension's kind of different while watching on TV than it would be on the field.
Takes more focus to imagine in real time.
Stop talking!
He's fast.
He's definitely got the speed.
I'd dribble past another if I were him.
Huh?
Oh, wow.
There's the triangle!
Those two guys just came over to cover.
They can help him shake off that creeper dude.
Okay. It looks like Kuribayashi is choosing to pass.
What did I say when I tell you?
They've got too many over on the right, so that's not an option.
Right now!
This is when I would pass it to him and then run into the goal from the left.
Whoa!
Out on right!
A big moment for Deguchi, who's in the clear!
Oh, nice save!
But what a killer pass from Kuribayashi!
Unbelievable!
His technique really is impressive.
He's also fearless.
That's what truly sets him apart.
For instance, that killer pass he made.
If it had been off by even an inch, the other team would have countered.
But he didn't hesitate for a second.
How?
How is this guy even real?
Aruiza Kuribayashi has only been on the field for five minutes.
But apparently that's all the time he needs to turn the game in his beerion's favor with one touch on the ball!
I'm sorry, man.
I gotta bring it.
Flashy individual plays whenever I get the chance.
I'll still contribute as a member of the team, I swear.
But I have to make the most of this as well.
I need people to remember who I am.
I don't ever want to go back to the bench again.
That's why I have to get every spectator here on my side.
Wow!
That was a close one!
How the heck does he do it?
And how can I be more like him?
His plays are phenomenal.
Unreal.
I was wondering what you would think after watching Kuribayashi play.
And it looks like I have an answer.
I'll remember it from my own feature reference.
Oh?
In this one interview he gave, Kuribayashi said something interesting.
Whatever the situation may be, he does the same thing.
Immediately comes up with four viable options.
And then he chooses one.
Four of them?
I don't have options!
I barely have one!
And to be honest, that's really all I can ever handle at any given moment!
Nothing more!
Then you'll have to expand your options.
Listen to me, by watching Kuribayashi's game, you could find something to incorporate into your own.
Take my advice.
Do it.
Or at the very least, give it some thought.
And these are the stars of today's match.
First, we have Deguchi, who scored two times.
And the assist for the winning goal goes to...
Haruhisa Kuribayashi.
What?
Who the heck is this guy?
You know, besides a total monster.
Don't expect him to be as surprised as you are about all this.
We've been watching him play since we were juniors.
We know what he's capable of.
For those of us who joined the academy during grade school, we were usually above average players before we even got here.
We all think we're going to be the top players in junior youth.
I mean, with our backgrounds, how could we not?
But when I saw Kuribayashi on the first day, I immediately thought,
man, guess I'll have to aim to be second best instead.
The number one spot's already taken.
Next, we have Kuribayashi.
Every time we see you in a match, it blows our minds that you're still in high school.
What a fantastic game you had today.
Well, I've been practicing with the first team, so I'm used to this level of play, if I'm being honest.
There was never really a moment where I felt like I couldn't keep up with them.
Well, you are absolutely on par with them, that's for sure.
So are you focusing on physical training?
If you do, your core will get stronger and you'll start bulking up.
And you won't be so thin.
He's like the Bane of all interviewers.
When they ask something useless, he just stares them down as if he knows what they're looking for.
Everyone knows he's difficult.
Okay, but how is that question worthless?
The way I see it, someone who talks up their physical training is probably hiding their lack of technique.
So why should I listen to outside opinions when I know what I need better than anyone?
There's only one possible exception to that, and it's Manager Fukuda of the Aspirion Youth Team.
Oh, well, thank you very much.
That's a wrap on our interviews with today's star players.
Yoshitsune, you're starting a different training regimen tomorrow.
Sure.
Okay, aside from those of you who live in the dorms, you're dismissing...
Someone who talks up their physical training is probably hiding their lack of technique.
I get it now.
He wasn't sliding being physical.
He was just stating his priorities.
Technique is more important to him than strength.
Makes sense.
He's clearly confident in his own level of skill.
Amazing.
Everything about Haruhisa Kurabayashi is blowing my mind.
I want to meet him.
No, I don't just want to meet him.
If you want to play with him, then make the A-team and do it as soon as possible.
Kurabayashi will undoubtedly return to the A-team at some point.
The sooner you join, the sooner you can show them your value.
And then hopefully by the time he gets back, the seed will have sprouted.
You'll be able to connect with him as a peer.
But in order to do that, you have to remember what I said earlier...
Adding something from Kurabayashi's game to my own, right?
I know exactly what it is!
You do?
Really?
Huh?
Uh...
Where's Hana?
Hmm?
What the...?
Everyone listen up!
Yoshitsune was injured in the match in Aomori.
So we'll be moving some of our front-line players from the B-team over to the A-team.
Fukuda said he'll be at our game this weekend.
He'll be determining who moves up.
This is a huge opportunity for you guys.
I don't know much at all.
About soccer, anyway.
I spent so much time revising these.
He said he wanted to eat whatever he wants, so I tried to make them more palatable.
And then...
I couldn't give them to him.
What am I saying?!
Literally all I had to do was hand them over!
Whatever!
I'm leaving!
You can do it, Ashito.
After that goal you made, moving up to the A-team is a real possibility.
And I promise.
I'll just watch from afar so that I don't get in your way.
Fukuda.
Don't forget what I said.
I'm serious about Aoi.
I think you...
The sooner the better.
Better for him, I mean.
If he can do what he needs to do in the next game, that's faster than I could have imagined.
You've been an excellent guide.
Thank you, Nozomi.
Hmm.
Aw, yeah!
I'm one lucky son of a you-know-what!
I'm playing a match every week!
What's with the screaming?
Where'd you get all this energy, man?
You're obviously tired.
Look at your face!
Hey there, Aoi.
I hear you've been working hard on your night training.
You still practicing kill it, then kick it?
Ha ha ha!
Well, maybe a little, but...
Just you wait and see!
I've learned something awesome from watching Kuribayashi play!
Hey, Aoi!
Huh?
So you ready to do this?
Hmm.
Yeah!
Watch, old man.
I'm moving up to the A-team after this.
Then it's all over!
It's a different team when you're here.
They're suddenly all motivated.
That's so.
Huh?
Otimo!
Move!
They've gotten so much better.
Hard to believe it's only been a week.
Middle.
Hmm.
There's an open space in the middle!
Why are you all getting drawn out?
Ah!
By watching Kuribayashi's game,
you could find something to incorporate into your own.
Take my advice.
Do it.
A killer pass!
Ooh?
What the heck?
Move up!
Come on!
Let's go!
Over there.
Kuribayashi's breaking free for a pass.
So that means I should aim there
so he gets it in midair.
One eye-opening.
Lightning killer pass!
Coming up!
What the crap!
What the hell was that?
Did they tell you which goal you were supposed to be aiming for?
Why?
Why isn't this stupid ball going where I want it?
Uh?
Huh?
I heard that you gave him some great advice at the barbecue place.
That's it?
Because it doesn't really seem to be working out for him.
I do not know what he thinks he's going to accomplish out there,
but his intentions are definitely interesting.
He's going to be making a mistake.
Twice he's made the exact same call.
Without any hesitation,
he's passing to players who are hidden behind opponents.
Excuse me.
Hmm?
Could you possibly tone it down a bit
and not speak to me so much?
Yeah, sure.
Keep it up.
I'm leaving the coaching to Nozomi.
I have just one thing to say,
and then I'll let you all get back to your talk.
Tell me,
why are you looking at us during play?
Are you playing this match against your manager?
Your opponents are in front of you,
on the field.
The positions you're given are yours.
Do not forget that.
It's strange.
Everyone seems a lot calmer now.
Were they really looking over at the bench during the game?
You're the one who should be watching me, old man.
An alley.
Uh, yeah.
Imitation isn't enough.
If you want to play like Kurabayashi,
then you should think about his movements.
A pass is a pass,
whether it's a so-called killer pass
or a short pass.
It's just a means of getting to the goal.
Those were supposed to be passes.
Wait, that's what he was doing?
I'm so confused.
A pass is a pass.
A means of getting to the goal.
Oh, wow.
I get it now.
That means it should go there.
If this pass works...
Ultimo!
He broke through on the right.
Easy.
Just block the shooting angle and we're good.
Guess I can't get to the middle now.
I know it's due.
It's...
Ashito's a weird kid.
I never expected him to score a goal like that.
A pass is just a pass
and a means of getting to the goal to score.
Wow.
Nice choice of words, Coach Nozomi.
What type of goal are you envisioning
when you pass the ball to another player?
A killer pass isn't killer until you can answer that.
You want to know what impressed me the most just now?
He envisioned himself scoring a goal
and worked backwards to make it a reality.
I'm Gabriel Batistuta, reincarnated!
I have returned!
And yes, I realize he's still alive!
Improving the precision of my passes is a given.
But what's most important to me is scoring.
I'm a forward!
And that's our ultimate drive!
Nozomi,
can you call him to the clubhouse later?
I'll tell him myself.
Understood.
I'm coming in!
Hm.
A sweeping three-to-zero victory.
Well done.
This was all you.
You made me do it.
Huh?
I'm loving soccer more each day.
There are so many things I can do now
that I couldn't do before.
Best part is that there is still a ton more left to learn.
Hm.
I am in such a good place right now.
And it's all because I met you.
Thanks, old man.
Will you move me to the A-team?
I'm not saying I'd be able to replace Yoshitsune right away.
I still have such a long way to go.
But I...
I can do this!
I'll get better!
We haven't spoken alone in a while, huh?
Not since the beach, I think.
I'm sorry, Ashito.
I can't promote you just yet.
Huh?
You can't?
But why?
Ashito,
turn yourself into a defender.
I could be more precise, couldn't I?
All right.
When you finally play on the world stage,
it'll be as a fullback.
You want me to be a defender?
I don't understand what you're saying.
Why?
Your skills are better suited for that position.
You will never again play as a forward.
A complete transition.
No!
Wait a sec.
I...
I'm a forward.
Are...
Are you saying...
that my play as a forward is no good?
That's who I am.
I did so well during this game!
I know I did!
And in the last one!
You did, and I'm not denying that.
Do you want to know why, though?
Because of your natural gift.
What?
And that gift cannot be put to best use
if you're on the front line.
By grasping the situation from the back,
you'll be...
I don't get what you're trying to say!
No!
I don't want to!
I came here because I want to become
the best forward in the world!
So then I owe it to you
to tell you why that'll never happen.
First, the ball doesn't stay at your feet.
That won't cut it on the A-team.
Then I'll go practice more!
I don't have any problems going late!
You are not agile.
There is no power at all
in your short sprints.
You're a slow mess
after the first 10 meters.
These things are fatal as a forward.
You do have a keen eye for scoring.
However, you don't have the ability
to back it up.
This isn't about the environment
that you're in.
It's not because you joined late.
It's a part of what's you.
At the moment you were born,
it had already been decided for you.
You were not meant to be a forward.
This was my plan from the start
when I first met you in Aimee.
I had a vacant hole at fullback
in my vision
and I knew you could fill it
like a missing puzzle piece.
What the hell are you saying?
If you knew I couldn't be a forward,
why didn't you tell me?
Why wait till now?
You wouldn't have come if I did.
This was the best time to do it.
No, I don't want to be a defender.
Please.
Please, old man.
Please, no.
If it's not what you want,
then you're certainly free to leave.
We can't hold onto players
we know will never be good enough.
Oh.
IE
Owie...
...
Thank you.
Next time on Awashi, it's just soccer.